Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Course Bulletins MC.286
New York University Archives
- NYU Abu Dhabi (RG 49), 2015-ongoing
  - NYU Abu Dhabi Bulletin 2021-2022, October 2021-March 2022 (Box Electronic Records)
    PDF of the NYU Abu Dhabi Bulletin for 2021-2022.
- NYU Shanghai (RG 50), 2013-ongoing
  - Bulletins (PDFs), 2013-2016; cuid17998 (Box Electronic Records)
  - NYU Shanghai Academic Bulletin, March 2015-ongoing (Box Electronic Records)
    Landing page linking to PDFs of the NYU Shanghai Bulletin. Contains the 2013-2014, 2014-2015, 2015-2016, 2016-2017, 2017-2018, and 2018-2019 bulletins and updates to the bulletins.
  - NYU Shanghai Majors and Minors, March 2015-ongoing (Box Electronic Records)
    Listing of all of the majors and minors offered at NYU Shanghai. Each major and minor links to a page describing the degree requirements, courses offered that semester, curriculum worksheets, faculty mentors, concentration options, and minor requirements.
  - NYU Shanghai Graduate and Advanced Education, September 2016-ongoing (Box Electronic Records)
    Information on graduate and advanced studies at NYU Shanghai. The webpage focuses on the Master's and PhD programs, research fellowship programs, study away programs in shanghai as well as news and events including convocation. Pages on the Master's program and PhD programs provide overviews and structures of the programs.
  - NYU Shanghai Undergraduate Bulletin Updates, May 2017-June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    Updates to the NYU Shanghai bulletins for bulletins from 2013-2019.
  - NYU Shanghai Core Curriculum, March 2019-ongoing (Box Electronic Records)
    This is the core curriculum page for New York University's Shanghai campus, which details general education requirements like Social & Cultural Foundations, Writing, Mathematics, Science, Algorithmic Thinking, and Language requirements. There is also information about specific courses that will fulfill these requirements and a short video by the academic advising office that discusses the NYU Shanghai core curriculum.
  - NYU Shanghai PhD Programs, March 2019-ongoing (Box Electronic Records)
    This page details PhD programs offered by NYU Shanghai, with links to pages for the individual programs detailing current supervising faculty, program structure, applications information, and profiles of current students. PhD programs include biology, chemistry, computer science, data science, mathematics, neural science, physics, and transportation planning and engineering.
  - NYU Shanghai Master's Programs, March 2019-ongoing (Box Electronic Records)
    This page details the Master's programs offered by NYU Shanghai, with links to pages for the individual programs. Masters programs include Data Analytics & Business Computing, Interactive Media Arts, Marketing and Retail Science, Organization Management and Strategy, Quantitative Finance, Social Work, and Teaching English to Speakers of Other Languages.
  - NYU Shanghai Undergraduate Bulletin 2019-2020, October 2019 (Box Electronic Records)
    PDF of undergraduate course bulletin for NYU Shanghai, featuring basic campus information, enrollment information, degree requirements, and course listings by degree program.
  - NYU Shanghai-NYU Stern Master of Science in Quantitative Finance Curriculum, October 2019-June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    Curriculum page for NYU Stern Shanghai's MS program in quantitative finance, including course listings and descriptions, as well as links to other information about this and other degree programs offered by Stern Shanghai.
  - NYU Shanghai-NYU Stern Master of Science in Data Analytics & Business Computing Curriculum, October 2019-June 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    Curriculum page for NYU Stern Shanghai's MS program in Data Analytics and Business Computing, including course listings and descriptions, and links to other pages on the NYU Stern Shanghai, including more information about this and other degree programs.
  - NYU Shanghai-NYU Stern Master of Science in Data Analytics and Business Computing, October 2020-June 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
    Overview of the Master of Science in Data Analytics and Business Computing taken at NYU Stern in New York and NYU Shanghai. The website contains the curriculum, course sequence and descriptions, faculty, and advisory board.
  - NYU Shanghai-NYU Stern Master of Science in Data Analytics and Business Computing Curriculum, October 2020-ongoing (Box Electronic Records)
  - NYU Shanghai-NYU Stern Master of Science in Quantitative Finance, October 2020-ongoing (Box Electronic Records)
    Overview of the Master of Science in Quantitative Finance taken at NYU Stern in New York and NYU Shanghai. The website contains the curriculum, course sequence and descriptions, faculty, and advisory board.
  - NYU Shanghai Undergraduate Bulletin 2020-2021, November 2020-March 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
    PDF of the NYU Shanghai undergraduate bulletin for 2020-2021.
  - NYU Shanghai-NYU Stern Master of Science in Marketing and Retail Science Curriculum, October 2021-ongoing (Box Electronic Records)
    Overview of the Master of Science in Marketing and Retail Science taken at NYU Stern in New York and NYU Shanghai. The website contains the curriculum, course sequence and descriptions, faculty, and advisory board.
  - NYU Shanghai-NYU Stern Master of Science in Organization Management & Strategy Curriculum, October 2021-ongoing (Box Electronic Records)
    Overview of the Master of Science in Organization Management and Strategy taken at NYU Stern in New York and NYU Shanghai. The website contains the curriculum, course sequence and descriptions, faculty, and advisory board.
  - NYU Shanghai Undergraduate Bulletin 2021-2022, November 2021-ongoing (Box Electronic Records)
    PDF of the NYU Shanghai undergraduate bulletin for 2021-2022.
- Rory Meyers College of Nursing (RG 52), May 2014-ongoing
  - Rory Meyers College of Nursing Academic Bulletin, April 2014-August 2018 (Box Electronic Records)
    The College of Nursing (NYUCN) offers a Bachelor of Science Degree with the major in Nursing; Master of Science and Post-Master's Advanced Certificate Programs; a Doctor of Philosophy in Research Theory and Development and a Doctor of Nursing Practice degree. The NYUCN, advancing humane and quality health care for a global society, is the strategic choice for nursing education in the 21st century.
  - Rory Meyers College of Nursing Academic Programs, May 2014-October 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    Website contains the academic program for the Rory Meyers College of Nursing Academic Programs. It contains the academic programs from the baccalaureate, master's, advanced certificates, and non-degree programs, focusing on curricula, eligibility, class schedules, academic calendars, academic bulletins, and how to apply to the programs.
  - Rory Meyers College of Nursing Academic Bulletin, October 2019 (Box Electronic Records)
    PDF of the Meyers College of Nursing academic bulletin for 2016-2017. This PDF is currently unable to playback in Wayback, contact the Web Archivist for access.
  - Rory Meyers College of Nursing Academic Bulletin Spring 2021, March 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
    PDF of the spring 2021 College of Nursing bulletin. This PDF is currently unable to playback in Wayback, contact the Web Archivist for access.
- College of Global Public Health (RG 53), October 2016-ongoing
  - College of Global Public Health Academic Programs, October 2016 (Box Electronic Records)
    Homepage for the academic program at the College of Global Public Health. Includes information on the undergraduate program, the master's program, the doctoral program, the advanced certificate, and the master of arts is bioethics.
  - College of Global Public Health Undergraduate Courses, October 2016-April 2017 (Box Electronic Records)
    This page describes the undergraduate courses offered for Global Public Health majors. It contains core course descriptions and syllabi, electives, study away global public health course descriptions, and 2016-2017 course schedules.
  - College of Global Public Health Cross-Continental MPH, October 2016-April 2017 (Box Electronic Records)
    Degree requirements of core and concentration courses for the Cross-Continental Master in Public Health.
  - College of Global Public Health Master of Public Health, October 2016-May 2017 (Box Electronic Records)
    Course schedules for the Master in Public Health as well as concentration degree requirements and sequences.
  - College of Global Public Health MA in Bioethics, October 2016-June 2017 (Box Electronic Records)
    Webpage containing course descriptions of the core degree requirements for the MA in Bioethics, course sequences, and course schedules for Fall 2016, Spring 2017, and Fall 2017.
  - College of Global Public Health Applied Global Public Health Certificate, April 2017 (Box Electronic Records)
    Course descriptions for the four courses included in the Applied Global Public Health Certificate.
  - College of Global Public Health Advanced Certificate in Public Health, April 2017 (Box Electronic Records)
    Listing of the five courses to complete the advanced certificate in public health program.
  - College of Global Public Health Social and Behavioral Sciences Concentration, May-July 2017 (Box Electronic Records)
    Webpage containing degree requirements and course sequences for the Social and Behavioral Sciences concentration.
  - College of Global Public Health Environmental Public Health Sciences Concentration, May-July 2017 (Box Electronic Records)
    Webpage containing degree requirements and course sequences for the Environmental Public Health Sciences concentration.
  - College of Global Public Health Community and International Health Concentration, May-July 2017 (Box Electronic Records)
    Webpage containing degree requirements and course sequences for community and international health concentration.
  - College of Global Public Health Biostatistics Concentration, May-July 2017 (Box Electronic Records)
    Webpage containing degree requirements, management specialization course sequence, and health policy specialization course sequence for the Public Health and Policy Management concentration.
  - College of Global Public Health Global Health Concentration, May-July 2017 (Box Electronic Records)
    Webpage containing degree requirements and course sequences for the global health concentration.
  - College of Global Public Health Public Health Nutrition Concentration, May-July 2017 (Box Electronic Records)
    Webpage containing degree requirements and course sequences for public health nutrition concentration.
  - College of Global Public Health Public Health Policy and Management Concentration, May-July 2017 (Box Electronic Records)
  - College of Global Public Health Epidemiology Concentration, May-July 2017 (Box Electronic Records)
    Webpage containing degree requirements and course sequences for epidemiology concentration.
  - NYU School of Global Public Health Master of Public Health Concentrations, May 2017-ongoing (Box Electronic Records)
    Landing page detailing the concentrations and their specialization checklists for the Master of Global Public Health at the School of Global Public Health. Concentrations include Biostatistics, Community Health Science and Practice, Environmental Public Health Sciences, Epidemiology, Global Health, Public Health Nutrition, Public Health Policy and Management, Social and Behavioral Sciences and Sustainable Development Goals.
  - College of Global Public Health Master of Public Health Courses, May 2017-ongoing (Box Electronic Records)
    Website containing information about courses offered for the master's degree in Public Health. It includes concentration degree requirements and class schedules.
  - College of Global Public Health Master of Public Health Course Descriptions, June-July 2017 (Box Electronic Records)
    Course descriptions for the Master of Public Health. Includes course numbers and semester offered.
  - College of Global Public Health Masters of Arts in Bioethics Courses, June 2017-October 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    Course sequences, electives offered in the College of Public Health and other NYU schools electives, and course schedules for the Masters of Bioethics.
  - College of Global Public Health Certificates Programs, June 2017-ongoing (Box Electronic Records)
    Landing page for the certificates offered at the College of Global Public Health. Certificate programs include the Advanced Certificate in Public Health, Advanced Certificate in Health and Human Rights, Advanced Certificate in Public Health Nutrition, Applied Global Public Health Certificate, Advanced Certificate in Public Health Disaster Science, Policy and Practice, and Advanced Certificate in Public Health Data Science.
  - College of Global Public Health Sustainable Development Goals Master of Public Health, July 2017-October 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    Website for the Sustainable Development Goals concentration for the Master of Public Health. From 2017-2018, it was considered a separate online master's program. In 2019, it became a concentration. The website contains the core courses, required zero credit courses, concentration courses, electives, and sample course sequences.
  - College of Global Public Health Undergraduate Courses, July 2017-March 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
    Website containing information about courses offered for the undergraduate degree in Public Health. It includes class schedules, core courses and syllabi, and electives offered.
  - College of Global Public Health PhD in Public Health Courses, November 2017-ongoing (Box Electronic Records)
    Degree requirements for pre-requisite courses, program sequences and Epidemiology, Social and Behavioral Sciences, and Public Health Policy Management concentration overviews and courses for the doctorate in Public Health.
  - College of Global Public Health Cross-Continental Master's in Public Health Courses, November 2017-October 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    This page lists course offerings for the Masters in Public Health program and links to syllabi for the individual courses, as well as other pages on the School of Public Health site for more information on the program.
  - College of Global Public Health Master of Public Health Course Descriptions, August 2018-June 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
  - College of Global Public Health Sustainable Development Goals Concentration, February 2019-ongoing (Box Electronic Records)
    Website for the College of Global Public Health Sustainable Development Goals concentration in the Master of Public Health program. The website contains information on the concentration, skills designated to be acquired in the program, course listings, and sample full-time and part-time course sequence.
  - College of Global Public Health Programs, March 2019-October 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
    This page features graduate program overviews for New York University's College of Public Health, including advanced certificates, master's programs in Public Health and Bioethics, undergraduate programs, and doctorate programs. The page features links to individual program pages where users can find program requirements and course sequences, doctorate student profiles, application information, and information about past student projects.
  - NYU School of Global Public Health Master of Science in Biostatistics, March 2019-ongoing (Box Electronic Records)
    Degree requirements, course sequences, and requirement checklists for the Master of Science in Biostatistics at the School of Global Public Health. Also includes a program comparison between the MS in Biostatistics and the MPH with a Biostatistics concentration.
  - Center for Bioethics Graduate Courses, October 2019-November 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
    Graduate course descriptions for classes offered at the Center for Bioethics starting in Summer 2019.
  - NYU School of Global Public Health Master of Science in Epidemiology, March 2020-ongoing (Box Electronic Records)
    Degree requirements, course sequences, and requirement checklists for the Master of Science in Epidemiology at the School of Global Public Health. Also includes a program comparison between the MS in Epidemiology and the MPH with a Epidemiology concentration.
  - NYU School of Global Public Health Fall 2021 Undergraduate Course Listings, June 2020-March 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
    PDF of course listings at the School of Global Public Health. This PDF is currently unable to playback in Wayback, contact the Web Archivist for access.
  - NYU School of Global Public Health Spring 2021 Undergraduate Course Listings, March 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
  - NYU School of Global Public Health Doctor of Public Health, October 2021-ongoing (Box Electronic Records)
    Degree requirements, course sequences, foundational competencies, and program-specific competencies for the Doctor of Public Health at the School of Global Public Health.
  - NYU School of Global Public Health Descriptions and Syllabi, October 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
    Descriptions and Syllabi for graduate, doctoral, and undergraduate courses at the School of Global Public Health.
  - Center for Bioethics Summer 2022 Graduate Courses, June 2022 (Box Electronic Records)
    Graduate course descriptions for classes offered at the Center for Bioethics in Summer 2022.
  - Center for Bioethics Fall 2022 Graduate Courses, October-November 2022 (Box Electronic Records)
- Non-course catalog publications
  - The Charter and the Statutes Defining the Organization and Government of New York University, 1909 (Box 179)
  - Tercentenary Accouncements 1609-1909 "Three Epochs in Education in New York City", June 1909 (Box 179)
  - The Alumni Electorate Secretary's Report, June 1910 (Box 179)
  - NYU Its Organization and Equipment, June 1911 (Box 179)
  - Address at the Opening of the Academic Year by Elmer Ellsworth Brown, September 1915 (Box 179)
  - The Charter and the Statutes Defining the Organization and Government of New York University, 1915 (Box 179)
  - Extracts from the Rules of the College of Arts and Pure Science and School of Applied Arts, June 1917 (Box 179)
  - Activities in Relation to the War, January 1918 (Box 179)
  - Roll of Honor, July 1918 (Box 179)
  - Announcement of Courses Opening on January First and February First, with Special Reference to the Needs o Soldiers and Sailors Recently Released from Service, December 1918 (Box 179)
  - General Information booklets, 1927-1936 (Box 179)
  - University Bibliography, 1931-1935 (Box 179)
  - A List of Reference Books with Descriptive Notes for Freshmen, 1933, 1935 (Box 179)
  - Bulletin: University Bibliography, 1950 (Box 201)